By purchasing and/or using this application, you agree to the terms of the End User License Agreement and EA’s Privacy Policy and Terms of Service.
Version
Firemint
Programmers
Programming
Engineers
Engineering
Artists
Art
Animator
Animation
Art and Animation
Designers
Design
Producer
Production
Audio
Sound Effects
Composer
Music
CEO
Design Director
Development Director
Technical Director
Art Director
QA
Director, Firemint
Director of Studio
Studio Director
Director
Firemint Director
Coming Soon!
Coming Soon
Connected to Cloudcell
Connected to Cloud Cell
Cloud Cell
Cloudcell
Notifications
Current Version
About
Pawsed
Paused
Restart
Return To Map
Exit To Map
CatMouse
SPYmouse
SPY mouse
SPY Mouse
S.P.Y.mouse
S.P.Y. mouse
S.P.Y. Mouse
Spy Mouse
Spy mouse
Spymouse
SpyMouse
Exit
Quit
Language
About
Story Mode
Stats
Statistics
Options
Achievements
Sync
Sound Effects
Sounds
Music
Back
Clear Save
Erase Save
Clear Save Game
Erase Save Game
Tip
MOUSEHOLES
Mouseholes are connected to other mouseholes of the same color.
MOUSETRAPS
Mousetraps are lethal!\n\nDisarm them with a dice, and steal the cheese!
FURNITURE
Sometimes furniture is the best place to hide!
BALL OF STRING!
If the cat is playing with string, you can sneak by unnoticed!
Drop the string where the cat will see it.
GET THE CHEESE!
Take the cheese to your mousehole!
FEAR THE CATS!
They will eat your face and show no mercy!\n\nUse mouseholes to escape!
Tap the DROP button to drop what you're carrying and run faster!
WIND UP MOUSE!
Pick it up and carry it with you!  \n\nYou can draw a path, and the mouse will lure the cats after it!
Tap the icon to activate the wind up mouse.
Transylvanian Bat Milk Cheese!
Wensleydale takes a plane to Transylvania, in search of the infamously rare and delicious bat's milk cheese.
Friends
Menu
More
Congratulations!
Erase Game Data?
This will erase all of your progress and cannot be undone!
Erase your progress? This cannot be undone!
Erase all of your progress? This cannot be undone!
Erase your game progress? This cannot be undone!
Cancel
Erase Data
Continue
Play!
Help
How to Play
Support
Visit our support site to let us know about problems, share ideas and ask questions. Please note: tapping "Get Support" will open a web browser.
Get Support
Loading
Credits
Quit
Special Item Found!
My Stuff
Your Stuff
Stuff!
Stuff
Scores!
Scores
Leaderboards
Leaderboard
My Squeak Friends
My SPY mouse Friends
Go!
Global
Overall
Totals
Total Game Score
Total Time Played
Total Distance Run (m)
Total Metres Run
Total Distance Run
Cheese Reclaimed
Cheeses
Pickups Found
Cat Deaths
Cat Fights
Trap Deaths
Caught in Traps
Trap Disarms
Trap Foils
Escapes
Exits
Mouseholes used
Mouseholes
Best Score
Best Dist
Date Best
Last Score
Last Distance
Last Date
Attempts
Wins
Victories
Attempts til Bronze
Attempts til Silver
Attempts til Gold
Attempts til Platinum
<locked>
Get your Agent Squeak friends to Squeak near you on their device!
Retrieving detailed data from Cloudcell
Name: 
Total Score: 
VS
Pickup %d of %d
Map: %d
UID: %d
Best Score: %i
Best Score: N/A
%s, CC Rank: Unranked
%s, CC Rank: > 10000th
%s, CC Rank: %s
%s, %i%% Game Completed
Rank
Name
Score
Super Agent
Special Agent
Secret Agent
Agent
Junior Agent
Unranked
Pair!
Threes!
Foursies!
Fives!
Mixed bag!
Pair!
Two Pair!
Three of a Kind!
Full House!
Four of a Kind!
Straight!
Flush!
Single!
Challenge Accepted
You'll need a score of more than 
 to beat 
Challenge Download Failed
You need to unlock this Level before you can Accept the Challenge
Please check your network connection and try again
Please download the latest version of Agent Squeak from iTunes and try again
Please download the latest version of SPY mouse from iTunes and try again
Please download the latest version of SPYmouse from iTunes and try again
Please download the latest version of S.P.Y. mouse from iTunes and try again
Please download the latest version of S.P.Y. Mouse from iTunes and try again
Please download the latest version of S.P.Y.mouse from iTunes and try again
Please download the latest version of S.P.Y.Mouse from iTunes and try again
Challenge details not found.
malformed url
Exit Bonus! x2
Time Bonus! +
%i Total
New Best Score
Your Score:
Agent Squeak Challenge
SPYmouse Challenge
Challenge is unavailable.
Level "
" has not been unlocked yet.
Logging in
Downloading challenge
Uploading result
Your prestigious score of 
 was too much for 
 to handle. They only had 
Commiserations!
With a score of 
 you were unable to best 
 and their score of 
Score:
Challenge: %d
Time:
Bonus:
Hidden Exit!
Hidden Area!
Please rate this map
Skip All
Give Us Feedback!
Map: '%s'
You must log in to Game Center using the Game Center application to view leaderboards.
You must set up an account on Cloudcell when prompted to view leaderboards.
You must log in to Game Center using the Game Center application to view player settings.
You must set up an account on Cloudcell when prompted to view player settings.
Submitting data to Cloudcell
Retrieving leaderboards from Cloudcell
Your ranking class: 
*** MISSING WORLD TEXT ***
*** MISSING LEVEL TEXT ***
Total:
New Best! 
You're ranked in the top
New Best Rank! 
Syncing Cloudcell
Next Medal: 
Score Required: 
Touch Screen To Continue
Time's up!
Try Again?
Cloudcell Error!
Click anywhere to continue
Initializing...
Squeaks %d
most squeaks ever %d
's iPhone
's iPod
Carrying: %d
Hey, I challenge you to beat my score in Agent Squeak! Go <a href="http://0005.midgard.paradise.cloudcell.com/Device/ChallengeAccept.php?nChallengeMemberId=%@">here</a> to accept!
Debug
Enjoying Agent Squeak?
Enjoying SPY mouse?
Are you enjoying SPY mouse?
Having fun with SPY mouse?
Are you having fun with SPY mouse?
Having fun playing SPY mouse?
Are you having fun playing SPY mouse?
Yes, rate it!
Don't ask again
Remind me later
News
Player Settings
Send Agent Squeak to your friend as a gift?
Send SPY mouse to your friend as a gift?
Send SPY mouse to a friend as a gift?
Give SPY mouse to a friend?
Gift SPY mouse to a friend?
Yes, please!
No
Grab the cheese and run!
Don’t let cats see you!
The bonus starts counting down when Agent Squeak starts moving!
The bonus starts counting down when SPY mouse starts moving!
Lure cats one way...
Then run around behind them!
Use mouse holes to sneak through walls!
Carry 2 cheese at once!
Matching cheese gives extra points.
Eat Me!
Follow, but don't get spotted!
Retry
You have found the %s special item. Tap on it in the main menu!
Space Helmet
Clipboard
Gift Box
PuzzleQuest Gem
Firemint Lotto Ticket
Flight Control Plane 
Sunglasses
Real Racing Car
Sunglasses
Keep Going!
Try Again!
Improved Score!
Improved Rank!
Okay
Secret Level!
Player Comparison
Your Scores
Unable to contact Cloudcell. Please check your connection and that CC Connectivity is enabled in options.
Uh oh!
My Profile
Squeak Mode
Resume
Main Menu
Game Data Deleted
Enjoy your journey again!
Enjoy playing SPY mouse again!
Enjoy your adventure again!
My Status
My Settings
Black cats come straight for you!
Use Television to hypnotise cats!
Blind cats don't chase you!
Hide!
Run and hide!
Balloons relieve the weight of cheese.
Buttons open and close doors.
Pipes spit you out the other end!
Some buttons need the weight of a cat.
Press the button for cheese!
Ninja cats throw stars!
Distract cats with string and fish.
Thief cats steal cheese!
Launch to the spot marked x!
Ghost cats float through walls!
Robo-dog gets cats! And carries cheese with ease!
Use Fake Mice on Mouse Traps!
Sleeping Cats are a Walkover!
Fire cats leave a deadly trail!
Pair!
Pair of Pairs!
Triple!
Full Mouse!
Four-Of-A-Kind!
Cheese Platter!
Five-Of-A-Kind!
x2
Mission
Accomplished!
Safe!
Home
You found a Special Item!
Where now for Agent Squeak?...
Where now for SPY mouse?...
All Cheese Crumbs
All Cheese Crumbs Within 00:10
All Cheese Crumbs Within 00:12
All Cheese Crumbs Within 00:30
All Cheese Crumbs Within 01:00
Without Balloons
Without Balloons Or Chillies
Without Balloons Or Fish
Without Balloons, Without Cheese Stolen
Without Balloons, Score 900
Cat Hits The Wall
Both Cats Hit The Wall
Both Cats Hit The Wall Within 00:10
3 Cats Hit The Wall
3 Cats Hit The Wall Within 00:25
Without Chillies
Without Chillies Or Balloons
Without Chillies Or Teacups
Only 1 Chilli
1 Five-Of-A-Kind Combo
1 Full Mouse Combo Within 00:20
1 Full Mouse Combo
2 Full Mouse Combos
3 Full Mouse Combos
1 Pair Combo
2 Pair Combos
3 Pair Combos
4 Pair Combos
1 Cheese Platter Combo
1 Cheese Platter Combo, Don't Get Spotted
2 Cheese Platter Combos
2 Cheese Platter And 2 Full Mouse Combos
2 Cheese Platter Combos, Don't Get Spotted
3 Cheese Platter Combos
1 Triple Combo
3 Triple Combos
5 Triple Combos
1 Pair Of Pairs Combo
Use Only 1 Shadowed Area
Without Fish
Without Furniture
Without Furniture Or Chillies
Only 1 Mouse Hole
Only 1 Path
Only 10 Paths
Only 2 Paths
Only 2 Paths, Don't Get Spotted
Only 3 Paths
Only 4 Paths
Only 4 Paths, Don't Get Spotted
Only 5 Paths
Only 6 Paths
Only 7 Paths
Only 8 Paths
Without Pipes
Without Pipes Or Safe Holes
Only 1 Pipe
Only 1 Pipe, Without Chillies
Only 1 Pipe, Score 530
Only 2 Pipes
Only 4 Pipes
Without Safe Holes
Without Safe Holes Or Balloons
Score 220
Score 2060
Score 2200
Score 950
Score 260
Score 1000
Score 550
Score 2100
Score 290
Score 540
Score 230
Score 95
Score 320
Score 80
Score 400
Score 485
Score 100
Score 60
Score 1600
Score 105
Only 4 Paths, Score 3600
Throwing Star Stuck In Your Cheese Trail
Throwing Star Stuck In Your Cheese
Don't Get Spotted
Don't Get Spotted, Score 260
Without Balloons, Don't Get Spotted
Without Chillies, Don't Get Spotted
Only Spotted Twice
Without Cheese Stolen
Without Balls of String
Without Teacups Or Chillies
Only 1 Teacup
Only 2 Teacups
Only 3 Teacups
Without Buckets
Only 1 Bucket
Within 00:10
Within 00:12
Within 00:15
Within 00:15, Only 4 Paths
Within 00:18
Within 00:20
Within 00:20, Only 4 Paths
Within 00:22
Within 00:22, Only 1 Path
Within 00:25
Within 00:25, Without Cheese Stolen
Within 00:30
Within 00:30, Without Safe Holes
Within 00:35
Within 00:35, Without Cheese Stolen
Within 00:40, Without Cheese Stolen
Within 00:45, Without Cheese Stolen
Within 00:40
Within 00:42
Within 00:45
Within 00:46
Within 00:05
Within 00:50
Within 00:55
Within 01:00, Don't Get Spotted
Within 01:10
Within 01:15
Within 01:20
Within 01:23
Within 01:30
Without Television
Without Television, Only 10 Paths
Without Buttons
Only 2 Buttons
Store
Clues
No clues unlocked yet!
Do you want to buy this item?
Would you like to buy this item?
Purchase
Special Items
It's a helmet
It's a gift
It's a gem
It's a Lotto
It's a plane
It's an olive
It's a car
It's sunglasses
Getting Items, please wait ...
Please wait …
Please log in to Cloudcell or Game Center to post to Facebook.
Please log in to Cloudcell to post to Facebook.
Please log in to Cloudcell to post to Twitter.
Please log in to Cloudcell to post to Twitter.
Cloudcell
Your post had been posted on Facebook!
You have posted to Facebook!
Your post had been posted on Twitter!
You have posted to Twitter!
About
Legal text.
Version
Legal
Behind the Scenes
Read the credits
Explorer Mouse
Find a Secret Level
Easy Way Out
Find a Hidden Level
Tell Your Friends
Post a Result to Twitter or Facebook
Post a Result to Twitter
Post a Result to Facebook
What Mouse?
Complete 20 Levels without being seen by Cats
Philanthropist
Have 25 pieces of cheese stolen
Completist
Complete all of the Hidden Levels
Complete all Hidden Levels
Boss 1 Crumbs & Traps
Complete 1-Boss With All Cheese Crumbs Collected and Traps Disarmed
Complete 1-Boss All Cheese Crumbs and Traps
Boss 2 Crumbs & Traps
Complete 2-Boss With All Cheese Crumbs Collected and Traps Disarmed
Complete 2-Boss All Cheese Crumbs and Traps
Boss 3 Crumbs & Traps
Complete 3-Boss With All Cheese Crumbs Collected and Traps Disarmed
Complete 3-Boss All Cheese Crumbs and Traps
Boss 4 Crumbs & Traps
Complete 4-Boss With All Cheese Crumbs Collected and Traps Disarmed
Complete 4-Boss All Cheese Crumbs and Traps
Boss 5 Crumbs & Traps
Complete 5-Boss With All Cheese Crumbs Collected and Traps Disarmed
Complete 5-Boss All Cheese Crumbs and Traps
Boss 6 Crumbs & Traps
Complete 6-Boss With All Cheese Crumbs Collected and Traps Disarmed
Complete 6-Boss All Cheese Crumbs and Traps
Pretty Good
Achieve one Goal in every Level
Top Work
Achieve two Goals in every Level
Super Achiever
Achieve all three Goals in every Level
pts
points
time bonus
time
time points
Tweet
Share
Results!
Exit Bonus! x 2
Achievement Points
Total Achievement Points: 
Play!
World
Support Us
Support Us!
Please Support Us
Please Support Us!
Secret Levels!
Want to play Secret Levels?
Play Secret Levels?
Like Us to Play!
Go to Facebook and Like us to Unlock the Secret Levels?
Like Us on Facebook to Unlock the Secret Levels?
Like Us on Facebook to Play the Secret Levels?
Like Us on Facebook to Play the Secret Levels!
Yes
No
Congratulations! All world goals have been achieved!
You did it! You achieved all the world goals!
Congratulations! You achieved all the world goals!
Congratulations! You got all the world goals!
You did it! You got all the world goals!
Play this world again to achieve all goals!
Play this world again to achieve all the remaining goals!
Re-play this world to achieve the remaining goals!
Play this world more to achieve all goals!
Play this world more to achieve all the remaining goals!
GOALS
World %d Completed
No!
SQUEEAK!
Submit
Next
Welcome %hs
Close Shave!
Busted!
Knockout!
New
Kiska is sleeping!
Please wait for %s hour(s).
Skipping Stages!
Kiska the Cat
Having trouble?
Kiska can help you by skipping a stage once an hour. You can find her in the paws menu
Kiska can help you by skipping a stage once an hour. You can find her in the pause menu
Kiska can skip this stage for you!
She will take the cheese and than nap for an hour!
Would you like Kiska to skip this stage now?
Yes!
No
Later
Please register for Cloudcell in order to make an In-App Purchase
In-App Purchase
Thank You
Your purchase was successful.
Cat trouble? Let the feisty Kiska help you out! Once per day, she'll knock out those nasty cats on any one level, making it a cinch to finish. Be warned, she'll take all the cheese as well! Kiska is a one-time purchase; once recruited, she's always there.\n
Kiska The Cat
Kiska the Cat
Welcome To Kiska!
Welcome to Kiska!
Kiska!
Kiska
A Cat Named Kiska
A Cat Called Kiska
Kiska Skips Levels
Kiska Wants To Join You!
Kiska Wants To Join You
…can help you pass levels!
…will help you pass levels!
Pass Levels!
Skip Levels!
…knocks out other cats!
…Knocks Out Other Cats!
…knocks out cats!
…Knocks Out Cats!
Hello there,
Hello there!
Hi there,
Hi there!
Greetings,
Greetings!
Hi Mr Squeak
Hi Mr Squeak!
Hi Mr Squeak,
Hello Mr Squeak!
Hello Mr Squeak,
Hello Mr Squeak
Hello SPYmouse
Hello SPYmouse!
Hello SPYmouse,
Hello SPY mouse
Hello SPY mouse!
Hello SPY mouse,
Hello SPY Mouse
Hello SPY Mouse!
Hello SPY Mouse,
Hello S.P.Y.mouse
Hello S.P.Y.mouse!
Hello S.P.Y.mouse,
Hello S.P.Y. mouse
Hello S.P.Y. mouse!
Hello S.P.Y. mouse,
Hello S.P.Y. Mouse
Hello S.P.Y. Mouse!
Hello S.P.Y. Mouse,
Hello Spy Mouse
Hello Spy Mouse!
Hello Spy Mouse,
Hello Spy mouse
Hello Spy mouse!
Hello Spy mouse,
I can help you pass levels by taking out other cats!
I can help you pass levels by taking out other cats.
I will help you pass levels by taking out other cats!
I will help you pass levels by taking out other cats.
I can help you pass levels!
I can help you pass levels.
I will help you pass levels!
I will help you pass levels.
I want to join your adventure! I can help you pass levels!
I want to join your adventure! I can help you pass levels.
I would love to join you in your adventure! I can help you pass levels!
I would love to join you in your adventure! I can help you pass levels.
She will help pass levels by taking out cats!
She will help pass levels by taking out the other cats!
If I join you on your adventure I will be able to help you once an hour in between my cat naps.
Have me on your adventure and I can help you once an hour in between my cat naps.
Let me join you and I'll help you once an hour in between my cat naps.
If you hire me to help you I will be available once an hour.
If you hire me to help you I will be available once an hour, in between cat naps.
Hire me! I will help once an hour!
I can help you skip levels once an hour in between naps!
I'll be available once an hour, between naps, to help you pass levels!
I'll be available once an hour, in between naps, to help you on your adventure!
Let's join forces against the cats! I will be free once an hour to help.
Hire me and I'll help you once an hour. I will take out the cats!
I will be available once an hour to beat up cats! I just need my naps in between.
Have me join you and you can call on me once an hour to help you skip levels!
Maybe Later
Only $0.99!
Skip This Level?
Skip this Level?
Pass This Level?
Pass this Level?
Want To Skip?
Want to Skip?
Would You Like To Skip?
Would you like to Skip?
I'm ready for action!
Would you like me to help you?
Would you like my help?
Kiska is ready for action!
I am available to help you!
I am available to assist you!
I am available!
I'll take out the cats so you can make clean your getaway!
I'll beat up the cats so you can make clean your getaway!
I'll remove the cats so you can make clean your getaway!
I'll take out the cats so you can get out of here!
I'll beat up the cats so you can get out of here!
I'll remove the cats so you can get out of here!
I'll take out the cats so you can get out!
I'll beat up the cats so you can get out!
I'll remove the cats so you can get out!
I'll take out the cats for you!
I'll beat up the cats for you!
I'll remove the cats for you!
I'll take out the cats!
I'll beat up the cats!
I'll remove the cats!
Then I shall need to take a nap for an hour.
I'd then need to nap for an hour.
Then I'd need to sleep for an hour!
Then take a nap!
Then sleep for an hour!
Then I'll be unavailable for an hour as I sleep!
And then we can meet again an hour later.
But I will need to sleep off my hard work for an hour!
Not Now Thanks
Not Now Thanks!
Not Right Now
Not Right Now!
Not Now Thank You
Not Now Thank You!
Yes Please!
Go For It!
Do Your Thing!
Yes!
Do It!
hours to go
hours remain
hour to go
hour remains
minutes to go
minutes remain
minute to go
minute remains
tap ribbons to view level goals
tap ribbons to view goals
tap ribbons to view
tap to view
tap to view goals
tap to view level goals
Tap Ribbons to View Level Goals
Tap Ribbons to View Goals
Tap Ribbons to View
Tap to View
Tap to View Goals
Tap to View Level Goals
Check the Paws Menu for Goals
Check the Pause Menu for Goals
Check the Paws Menu for Level Goals
Check the Pause Menu for Level Goals
Goals can be found in the Paws Menu
Goals can be found in the Pause Menu
Look in the Paws menu for Goals
Look in the Pause menu for Goals
Look in the Paws menu for Level Goals
Look in the Pause menu for Level Goals
Goals to aim for can be found in the Paws menu
Goals to aim for can be found in the Pause menu
Level Goals to aim for can be found in the Paws menu
Level Goals to aim for can be found in the Pause menu
Level Goals can be found in the Paws menu
Level Goals can be found in the Pause menu
Open the Paws menu to view Level Goals
Open the Pause menu to view Level Goals
Agent Squeak can now carry up to 2 pieces of cheese at a time!
Agent Squeak can now carry 2 pieces of cheese at a time!
Agent Squeak can now carry up to 2 pieces of cheese!
Agent Squeak can now carry 2 pieces of cheese!
Squeak can now carry up to 2 pieces of cheese at a time!
Squeak can now carry 2 pieces of cheese at a time!
Squeak can now carry up to 2 pieces of cheese!
Squeak can now carry 2 pieces of cheese!
SPYmouse can now carry up to 2 pieces of cheese at a time!
SPYmouse can now carry 2 pieces of cheese at a time!
SPYmouse can now carry up to 2 pieces of cheese!
SPYmouse can now carry 2 pieces of cheese!
You can now carry up to 2 pieces of cheese at a time!
You can now carry 2 pieces of cheese at a time!
You can now carry up to 2 pieces of cheese!
You can now carry 2 pieces of cheese!
Agent Squeak can now carry up to 3 pieces of cheese at a time!
Agent Squeak can now carry 3 pieces of cheese at a time!
Agent Squeak can now carry up to 3 pieces of cheese!
Agent Squeak can now carry 3 pieces of cheese!
Squeak can now carry up to 3 pieces of cheese at a time!
Squeak can now carry 3 pieces of cheese at a time!
Squeak can now carry up to 3 pieces of cheese!
Squeak can now carry 3 pieces of cheese!
SPYmouse can now carry up to 3 pieces of cheese at a time!
SPYmouse can now carry 3 pieces of cheese at a time!
SPYmouse can now carry up to 3 pieces of cheese!
SPYmouse can now carry 3 pieces of cheese!
You can now carry up to 3 pieces of cheese at a time!
You can now carry 3 pieces of cheese at a time!
You can now carry up to 3 pieces of cheese!
You can now carry 3 pieces of cheese!
Agent Squeak can now carry up to 4 pieces of cheese at a time!
Agent Squeak can now carry 4 pieces of cheese at a time!
Agent Squeak can now carry up to 4 pieces of cheese!
Agent Squeak can now carry 4 pieces of cheese!
Squeak can now carry up to 4 pieces of cheese at a time!
Squeak can now carry 4 pieces of cheese at a time!
Squeak can now carry up to 4 pieces of cheese!
Squeak can now carry 4 pieces of cheese!
SPYmouse can now carry up to 4 pieces of cheese at a time!
SPYmouse can now carry 4 pieces of cheese at a time!
SPYmouse can now carry up to 4 pieces of cheese!
SPYmouse can now carry 4 pieces of cheese!
You can now carry up to 4 pieces of cheese at a time!
You can now carry 4 pieces of cheese at a time!
You can now carry up to 4 pieces of cheese!
You can now carry 4 pieces of cheese!
Agent Squeak can now carry up to 5 pieces of cheese at a time!
Agent Squeak can now carry 5 pieces of cheese at a time!
Agent Squeak can now carry up to 5 pieces of cheese!
Agent Squeak can now carry 5 pieces of cheese!
Squeak can now carry up to 5 pieces of cheese at a time!
Squeak can now carry 5 pieces of cheese at a time!
Squeak can now carry up to 5 pieces of cheese!
Squeak can now carry 5 pieces of cheese!
SPYmouse can now carry up to 5 pieces of cheese at a time!
SPYmouse can now carry 5 pieces of cheese at a time!
SPYmouse can now carry up to 5 pieces of cheese!
SPYmouse can now carry 5 pieces of cheese!
You can now carry up to 5 pieces of cheese at a time!
You can now carry 5 pieces of cheese at a time!
You can now carry up to 5 pieces of cheese!
You can now carry 5 pieces of cheese!
Go to Safe Holes to eat cheese!
Safe Holes are great when there's too much cheese to carry!
Munch cheese in Safe Holes!
Eat cheese in Safe Holes!
Go to Safe Holes to eat cheese!
Safe Holes are safe!
Free up your paws in Safe Holes!
Free your paws in Safe Holes!
Get to Safe Holes to free your paws of cheese!
Get to Safe Holes when you're paws are full!
Get to Safe Holes to munch your cheese!
Safe Holes!
Visit Safe Holes to eat your cheese!
Visit Safe Holes to eat the cheese!
Safe Holes score cheese!
Free your paws and score your cheese in Safe Holes!
Free your paws and the score will follow in Safe Holes!
Score cheese in Safe Holes!
Gain score for your cheese combos in Safe Holes!
Unlimited use Kiska
Ah Mr Squeak, I've been expecting you. I will leave you to suffer your demise!
Ah Mr Squeak, I've been expecting you.
Ah SPY mouse, I've been expecting you. I will leave you to suffer your demise!
Good day Mr Squeak, I've been expecting you. I will leave you to suffer your demise!
Good day Mr Squeak, I've been expecting you.
Good day SPY mouse, I've been expecting you. I will leave you to suffer your demise!
Good day SPY mouse, I've been expecting you.
Not you again.
Mr Squeak, we meet again.
SPY mouse, we meet again.
Back again, Mr Squeak?
Back for more, Mr Squeak!
Back again, SPY mouse?
Back for more, SPY mouse?
You're back!
Back again I see.
Sucker for punishment?
You can't get enough, can you, Mr Squeak?
You can't get enough, can you, SPY mouse?
You have a lot of nerve for a little mouse, Mr Squeak.
You have a lot of nerve for a little mouse.
You're back again. And I thought you'd be cat food by now.
So you're back again to suffer your demise Mr Squeak.
You've returned to suffer your demise in a whole new way I see Mr Squeak.
Next World
Previous World
Cheese!
Pussy Cat Patrol
Double Trouble
Catch Me If You Can
Pass The Pounce
Cheesy Does It
Sleepy Walkover
Mouse Holes
Fake Mouse
Two By Two
Born To Run
Triple Trouble
Grate Expectations
Run For Your Life
Tune In, Drop Out
Mind Control
Snack Time
Three Blind Cats
Pair Of Pairs
Three Of A Kind
He Who Hides, Wins
Storm In A Teacup
On The Prowl
Take A Weight Off
Cheese Galore
Knives & Forks
Step On
Pipe Work
Chase Me!
Open & Shut Case
Mind The Gap
Magical Factory Tour
Over Here!
Getta Goudas
Tasty Yellow Beef
Around & Around
Beau Fort
The Cleaner
Cherry Pop
Prime Time
All For One
Diving And Ducking
Cat Distraction
Danablu Dojo
Full Mouse
Strung Along
Alley Way
Garden Dreams
Mouse In The Middle
Throwing Stars
Inner City Pressure
Gears Of Paw
Back And Forth
Blast Off
Split Sides
Piano Mouse
In And Out
Wigmore Heights
A Purfect Day
Cheese Fun Do
Park Life
Junkyard Jibe
The Four Traps
Nobody's Lunch
Haunted Havarti
Cursed Curd
Kitty Ghosts
Two Types Of Trouble
Rooms Of Spook
Trip The Switch
Foiled By Fakes
Two Worlds Collide
Spread Of Spectres
Pesky Pipes
Purfect Timing
A Fiendish Game
Edamned
Four Feline Foes
Hide In Sheet
Run For Your Pipe
Welcome To The Jungle
Fireball Frenzy
Hide And Sneak
Fresh Fromage
Thou Shalt Not Steal
Woof Woof!
Take That
Red Hot
World 7 Bonus Level
NEED TEXT - BOSS WORLD 7
Get Over It
Release The Hound
On And Off
Safe In The Centre
Park The Pooch
Cats And Cannons
Gauntlet Of Fire
Halouminati
Deeper Underground
Hide In Fido
Blind Guardians
Fluffy vs Squeak
Grand Finale
Safe Holes!
Cheese Slots!
Carry More!
Carry More!
Level Goals!
EULA
Privacy Policy
Terms of Service
End User Licence Agreement
Application End User Licence Agreement
EA's End User Licence Agreement
Terms of Service
EA's Privacy Policy
Stay tuned, things are heating up!
The adventure continues this Fall..
All new fiery update coming soon!
Play our other great games!
Available now on the App Store
Real Racing 2
Flight Control
Grab the cheese and run!
Grab the cheese!
Sneak for your life!
Run for your life!
Avoid the cats!
6 worlds of delicious adventure
Explore 6 worlds of tasty adventure
Master 72 challenging levels
Be smart... or be eaten!
Be sneaky... or be eaten!
Sneak... or be snacked!\n\n
Draw Paths to Cheese then Exit Holes!
Avoid Cats!
Time doesn't start until Agent Squeak starts moving in each room.
Collect combinations of Cheese…
…to take to Safe Holes to score!
Exit Holes score double!
spy
mouse
mice
secret
agent
squeak
squeek
line
path
draw
casual
fun
game
stealth
sneak
adventure
SPY mouse is a trademark of Firemint Pty Ltd.
© 2012 Firemint Pty Ltd.
Disable Usage Sharing
Enable Usage Sharing
Help EA improve products, services and user experience by sharing usage information such as game statistics, settings, feature preferences and incident or event data.  This information will not be shared with any third party in a way that can personally identify you.  Disable usage sharing?
Sharing of usage statistics has been disabled for this game.  Help EA improve products, services and user experience by sharing usage information such as game statistics, settings, feature preferences and incident or event data.  This information will not be shared with any third party in a way that can personally identify you.  Enable usage sharing?
SPY mouse requires more free space on your device, please free up some space and restart the game.
Do you want to restart with new language setting?
Language Setting
Buy
Buy!
Marketing
Special Thanks
Challenge
Extra Challenge
Challenge Pack
Level Pack
Challenge Level
Extra Challenge Pack
Extra Level Pack
Extra Challenge Pack
Extra Mission
Special Mission
Extra Level
Special Level
Extra Challenges
Challenge Packs
Level Packs
Challenge Levels
Extra Challenge Packs
Extra Level Packs
Extra Challenge Levels
Extra Missions
Special Missions
Extra Levels
Special Levels
Challenge Accomplished!
Challenge Completed!
Challenge Achieved!
Challenge Over!
Stage
Stages
Extra Stages
Additional Stages
Unlock Extra Stages
Unlock Additional Stages
Difficult extra missions for Agent Squeak to accomplish
Difficult extra missions for Agent Squeak to undertake
Challenging extra levels for Agent Squeak
Challenging additional levels for Agent Squeak
Challenging extra levels for Agent Squeak to attempt
Difficult extra levels for Agent Squeak to attempt
Challenging additional levels for Agent Squeak to attempt
Difficult additional levels for Agent Squeak to attempt
Extra challenging additional levels for Agent Squeak
Challenging extra missions for Agent Squeak
Extra challenging additional levels
Challenging additional levels
Difficult extra challenges
Difficult additional levels
Extra difficult cheese chasing levels!
Extra difficult cheese chasing challenges!
More cheese chasing challenges!
You have unlocked an Extra Challenge!
You have unlocked Extra Challenges!
You have a new Extra Challenge!
You have new Extra Challenges!
Extra Challenge available!
Extra Challenges available!
Extra Challenge unlocked!
Extra Challenges unlocked!
Add X Squeak Friends to unlock  
Add 1 Squeak Friend to unlock  
Find X Squeak Friends to unlock  
Find 1 Squeak Friend to unlock  
X Squeak Friends required
1 Squeak Friend required
Add X Squeak Friends
Add 1 Squeak Friend
Add a Squeak Friend
Find X Squeak Friends
Find 1 Squeak Friend
Find a Squeak Friend
Requires %d Squeak Friends
Requires 1 Squeak Friend
Requires a Squeak Friend
Add Squeak Friends to access Extra Challenges
Add Squeak Friends to try Extra Challenges
Add Squeak Friends for access
Add Squeak Friends for Extra Challenges
Make X Friends in Squeak in Space to unlock Extra Challenges
Make X Friends via Squeak in Space to unlock Extra Challenges
Make a Friend in Squeak in Space to unlock Extra Challenges
Make a Friend via Squeak in Space to unlock Extra Challenges
Add friends via Squeak In Space
Find friends via Squeak In Space
Add friends in Squeak In Space
Find friends in Squeak In Space
You can add friends via Squeak In Space
You can find friends via Squeak In Space
You can add friends in Squeak In Space
You can find friends in Squeak In Space
Visit Squeak In Space to add Squeak Friends
Squeak In Space allows you to add Squeak Friends
Friend
Friends
Squeak Friend
Squeak Friends
Buddy
Buddies
Squeak Buddy
Squeak Buddies
Squeaker
Squeakers
Squeak In Space
Squeak In Space Unlocked
Squeak In Space is unlocked
Squeak In Space Mode
Squeak Mode
Squeak Friends
Squeak Friends Mode
You're all alone! You should add your first Squeak Friend
It's pretty lonely out here in space, add your first Squeak Friend!
You can add Squeak Friends in Space, try it! 
It's Agent Squeak!
There's Agent Squeak!
Agent Squeak appeared!
You now have 1 Squeak Friend
You now have X Squeak Friends 
You have 1 Squeak Friend
You have X Squeak Friends
Find more when other players nearby are in Squeak in Space
Find more when other players close by are in Squeak in Space
Find more when other players nearby enter Squeak in Space
Find more when other players close by enter Squeak in Space
Add more when other players nearby are in Squeak in Space
Add more when other players close by are in Squeak in Space
Add more when other players nearby enter Squeak in Space
Add more when other players close by enter Squeak in Space
Enter Squeak in Space with players nearby to add Squeak Friends
Enter Squeak in Space with players close by to add Squeak Friends
Enter Squeak in Space with players nearby to find Squeak Friends
Enter Squeak in Space with players close by to find Squeak Friends
Squeaking!
Try Squeaking!
Let's Squeak!
Tap yourself to Squeak!
Tap your mouse to Squeak!
Tap your space mouse to Squeak!
Add friends
Add more friends
Add Squeak Friends
Add more Squeak Friends
Add X Squeak Friends
Find Squeak Friends to unlock Extra Challenges
Find Squeak Friends to access Extra Challenges
Add Squeak Friends to unlock Extra Challenges
Add Squeak Friends to access Extra Challenges
Adding Squeak Friends unlocks Extra Challenges
Finding Squeak Friends unlocks Extra Challenges
Adding Squeak Friends awards you Extra Challenges
Finding Squeak Friends awards you Extra Challenges
More Squeak Friends means more Extra Challenges!
Add more Squeak Friends to unlock more Extra Challenges!
You unlocked Squeak In Space!
You have unlocked Squeak In Space!
Try it out now and learn all about Squeak Friends!
Try out Squeak In Space to learn about Squeak Friends!
If anybody else nearby is in Space, you will Squeak for them too!
If anybody else close by in Space, you will Squeak for them too!
If any other players nearby are in Space with you, you will Squeak for them too!
If any other players close by are in Space with you, you will Squeak for them too!
Squeak with others nearby to add them as friends and unlock extra content!
Squeak with others nearby to add them as friends and unlock extra challenges!
Squeak with others nearby to add them as friends and unlock extra challenges and features!
Squeak with other players nearby to add them as friends and unlock extra content!\nSqueak with other players nearby to add them as friends and unlock extra challenges!\nSqueak with other players nearby to add them as friends and unlock extra challenges and features!\n
Squeak with other players nearby to add them as friends and unlock extra challenges!
Squeak with other players nearby to add them as friends and unlock extra challenges and features!\n
Squeak with other players close by to add them as friends and unlock extra content!\n
Squeak with other players close by to add them as friends and unlock extra challenges!
Squeak with other players close by to add them as friends and unlock extra challenges and features!
Squeak with friends nearby and unlock extra content!
Squeak with friends nearby and unlock extra challenges!
Squeak with friends nearby and unlock extra challenges and features!
Squeak with others nearby to add new friends!
Squeak with other players nearby to add new friends!\n
Squeak with other players close by to add new friends!\n
Squeak with other players close by to unlock extra content!
Squeak with other players close by to unlock extra challenges!
Squeak with other players close by to unlock extra challenges and features!
Squeak with friends nearby and unlock extra content!
Squeak with friends nearby and unlock extra challenges!\n
Squeak with friends nearby and unlock extra challenges and features!
Add new friends to unlock extra content!
Add new friends to unlock extra challenges!\n
Add new friends to unlock extra challenges and features!\n
Add more friends to unlock extra content!\n
Add more friends to unlock extra challenges!
Add more friends to unlock extra challenges and features!
Add more new friends to unlock extra content!\n
Add more new friends to unlock extra challenges!
Add more new friends to unlock extra challenges and features!
Squeak in Space to add new friends and unlock extra content!
Squeak in Space to add new friends and unlock extra challenges!\n
Squeak in Space to add new friends and unlock extra challenges and features!
Squeak in Space to add new Squeak Friends!\n
Backpack
Briefcase
My stuff
Squeak Stuff
SPY Stuff
Squeak's Backpack
Agent Squeak's Backpack
My backpack
Agent's Squeak's SPY Stuff
You found a backpack!
You found your backpack!
It's a backpack!
This is your backpack, it holds important extra stuff
This is your backpack, it holds important extra features
This is your backpack, it holds all your extra tools
This is your backpack, it holds all your extra spy stuff
This is your backpack, it holds all your important extra things
Your backpack holds important extra features and challenges
Your backpack holds important extras tools and features
Your backpack holds extra features and challenges
Your backpack holds extra tools and features
Open your backpack to access to Squeak in Space
Tap on your backpack to try out Squeak in Space
Tap on your backpack to access it!
Tap on your backpack to open it!
Tap on your backpack to see what's inside!
Open your backpack to see what's inside!
Let's see what's inside!
Tap on your backpack to see what's inside!
Open it now to see what's inside!
Open it up to see what's inside!
Your backpack is always accessible on the world map
Open your backpack by tapping its icon on the top right
Your backpack is always available on the world map
Open your backpack at any time, just tap it on the world map
There is a new item in your backpack!
There are new items in your backpack!
Something new is in your backpack!
There are some new things in your backpack!
Something has been added to your backpack!
Is there something new in your backpack?
New!
Check your backpack regularly for extra features and challenges!
Check your backpack regularly for new items!
New items will appear in your backpack, it will glow when they do
Your backpack will glow when there's something new inside!
It's in your backpack!
Check your backpack!
Have a look inside your backpack!
It's been added to your backpack!
Find them in your backpack!
Find it in your backpack!
Locked
Unlocked
Tap me to activate!
Tap me!
Watch This Space…
Stay Tuned…
Extra Morsels…
World Select
World Access
Worlds
Quick Travel
Squeak Express
Fast access to all the worlds you've visited!
With World Select you can quickly access all the worlds you've visited!
Use World Select to quickly move between worlds
Quickly move between worlds!
Use World Select to switch quickly between worlds
Complete World 1 to unlock World Select
Complete 1 world to access World Select
Reach World 2 to unlock World Select
You need to reach World 2 to unlock World Select
Worlds are unlocked as your complete them during your adventure
Complete worlds to unlock them in World Select
As you reach each new world, it will become available in World Select
Complete worlds to allow speedy access to them via World Select
You found a space helmet!
Your found your space helmet!
You've retrieved your space helmet!
You found Agent Squeak's space helmet!
Locate the space helmet in your backpack to see what it does!
The space helmet is now in your backpack, find it and see what it does!
The space helmet can be found in your backpack! Go and see what it does!
The space helmet has unlocked Squeak In Space!
The space helmet allows you to Squeak in Space!
With the space helmet, you can now Squeak In Space!
In Squeak In Space you can find friends and Squeak with them!
In Squeak In Space you can add friends and Squeak with them!
Squeak In Space to get more Squeak Friends!
Squeak In Space to add more Squeak Friends!
Squeak In Space to find more Squeak Friends!
Squeak in Space! Add more friends!
Squeak In Space is available in your Backpack!
You can find Squeak In Space in your Backpack!
Try Squeak In Space, it's inside your Backpack!
Squeak In Space is in your backpack!
Find Squeak In Space in your backpack!
Your backpack holds important extra features! Check it out!
Check Agent Squeak's backpack for extra features!
Check your backpack for extra features!
Check Agent Squeak's backpack for extras!
Check your backpack for extra SPY mouse features!
Your backpack holds extra SPY mouse features! 
Your backpack holds additional SPY mouse features and challenges!
New features will appear in your backpack!
Check your backpack regularly for new features and challenges!
Agent Squeak's backpack holds extra features and challenges!
Agent Squeak's backpack holds extra features!
Tap it to open it!
Tap it to see what's inside!
Care to stay for dinner?
Nom nom nom
blaarghh ... !
Challenges
Like Us!
Origin Leaderboards
Tap the Origin icon and log in to view leaderboards.
Log in to Origin to view leaderboards.
Log in
The Origin network could not be reached. Please check your network connection and try again.
%s logged in
%s logged out
Not logged in
Playing as %s
You have been logged out of Origin
Playing as Guest
Achievement awarded!
Requires Bluetooth or Wi-Fi connection.
Dossier
Dossiers
Profile
Profiles
You’ve found a dossier!
You’ve found a profile!
You've picked up a dossier!
You've picked up a profile!
These contain extra tips for aiding you in your daring missions! Collect them all and view them again in your backpack.
Dossiers contain extra tips for aiding you in your daring missions! Collect them all and view them again in your backpack.
Profiles contain extra tips for aiding you in your daring missions! Collect them all and view them again in your backpack.
Dossiers contain helpful information that can aid you in your adventure! Collect them all and view them again at any time via your backpack.
Profiles contain helpful information that can aid you in your adventure! Collect them all and view them again at any time via your backpack.
Dossiers contain extra information on the various enemies and items you'll encounter throughout your adventure. Collect them all and view them again in your backpack.
Profiles contain extra information on the various enemies and items you'll encounter throughout your adventure. Collect them all and view them again in your backpack.
Dossiers give you bonus intel on enemies and items you'll encounter during your adventure. You can view dossiers you've found in your backpack. See if you can collect them all!
Dossiers give you bonus intel on enemies and items you'll encounter during your adventure. You can view dossiers you've found in your backpack. See if you can collect them all!
Dossiers contain extra intel on the various enemies and items you'll encounter throughout your adventure. Collect them all and view them again in your backpack.
Profiles contain extra intel on the various enemies and items you'll encounter throughout your adventure. Collect them all and view them again in your backpack.
Type: 
Ninja Cat
Karate Cat
Warrior Cat
Blind Cat
Cool Cat
House Cat
Brown Cat
Scary Cat
Alley Cat
Black Cat
Ghost Cat
Spooky Cat
Phantom Cat
Thief Cat
Bandit Cat
Robber Cat
Types: 
Ninja Cats
Karate Cats
Warrior Cats
Blind Cats
Cool Cats
House Cats
Brown Cats
Scary Cats
Alley Cats
Black Cats
Ghost Cats
Spooky Cats
Phantom Cats
Thief Cats
Bandit Cats
Robber Cats
Balloon
Balloons
Teacup/Bucket
Teacups/Buckets
Teacup
Teacups
Bucket
Buckets
Chilli
Chillies
Cheese Machine
Cheese Machines
Television
Televisions
Cannon
Cannons
Mouse Cannon
Mouse Cannons
Fish/String
Fish/Ball of String
Fish/Balls of String
Fish
String
Ball of String
Balls of String
Button
Buttons
Cat Button
Cat Buttons
Fake Mouse
Fake Mice
Wind-up Mouse
Wind-up Mice
Last known whereabouts: 
Last seen:
Last seen in:
First appearance:
First appears in:
Known information:
Miscellaneous information:
Misc. information:
Known facts:
Facts:
Fun fact:
Fun facts:
Tips:
Extra tips:
Useful tips:
Handy hints:
Hints:
Detailed information:
Details:
Trivia:
Trivial information:
Extra information:
Intelligence:
Intel:
Rumours:
Rumoured information:
Rumoured facts:
Extra facts:
Extra Intel:
Scary cats come straight for you!
Alley cats come straight for you!
Level
These cats attack on sight, throwing a punishing stream of ninja stars
This cat attacks on sight, throwing a punishing stream of ninja stars
Stay on the move and time your cheese runs carefully
Stay focussed and time your paths carefully
Their razor sharp ninja stars can open a tin of cat food at 20 paces
This cat throws razor sharp ninja stars that can open a tin of cat food at 20 paces
Try hiding behind your cheese, if you please
Try using your cheese trail as a handy (and tasty) shield
Trained by fashion designer and ronin master Neko (The Claw)
They may look cute, but they’ll attack on sight
It may look cute, but this cat attacks on sight
They may be your most easily evaded foes, but they are still as crafty as… Cats.
This may be your most easily evaded foe, but it is still as crafty as… A cat.
Lure, tease and mock them all you want, but they'll make you pay if you're too slow to escape
Lure, tease and mock this moggie all you want, but it'll make you pay if you're too slow to escape
"Thousands of years ago, cats were worshipped as gods. They have never forgotten this." Anon
They hang around the house all day and sleep a lot… Pure evil!
This cat hangs around the house all day and sleeps a lot. Pure evil.
If they spot you, you'd better run and hide
If it spots you, you'd better run and hide
They don’t give up until they get their mouse (and eat it too)
It won't give up until it gets its mouse (and eats it too)
"Alley Cats in the house, our dinner is mouse" (Old Alley Cat song from the ‘80s)
"Scary Cats in the house, our dinner is mouse" (Old Alley Cat song from the ‘80s)
"Black Cats in the house, our dinner is mouse" (Old Alley Cat song from the ‘80s)
These are the type of cats that only true  cat lovers can appreciate
This is the type of cat that only a true cat lover can appreciate
Be vigilant or they’ll steal cheese right out from under your tail
Be vigilant or it will steal cheese right out from under your tail
Pilfering, plundering, scrounging swindlers, all of them
A pilfering, plundering, scrounging swindler
These cats give a whole new meaning to the term ‘cat burglar’
This cat gives a whole new meaning to the term ‘cat burglar’
They don’t even eat cheese, they just steal it to be as irritating and unlikeable as possible
This cat doesn’t even eat cheese, it just steal yours to be as irritating and unlikeable as it possibly can
Ain't no meow about it, these cats can pass straight through walls!
Ain't no meow about it, this cat can pass straight through walls!
These cats can pass straight through walls, straight through walls I tell you!
This cat can pass straight through walls, straight through walls I tell you!
Hide in the shadows to get them off your tail
Hide in the shadows to get this cat off your tail
What Ghost Cats? Where?
What Ghost Cat? Where?
I ain't afraid of no Ghost... Cat
Ghost Cats! Hahaha… ha…ha... hold me
They keep to their paths, patiently waiting for you to make a mistake
It will keep to its path, patiently waiting for you to make a mistake
They may seem harmless but don’t get too close…
It may seem harmless but don’t get too close…
They may not see all that well, but they’ll keep to their paths and wait for you to make your final, fatal mistake
It may not see all that well, but it will keep to its path and wait for you to make a final, fatal mistake
Guide dogs are out of the question!
Seeing-eye dogs need not apply!
Cats wearing sunglasses, I can dig that
A cat wearing sunglasses, I can dig that
Carrying too much cheese? Feeling heavy? Grab a balloon to ease your load
Sorry to burst your bubble, but balloons don’t like being taken into hiding spots
Balloons are also useful at parties
A balloon is an inflatable flexible bag filled with a gas
Michael Faraday invented the rubber balloon in 1824, he was not an avid gamer
We’ve already established that television is boring, but not to cats!
Turn on a television and marvel at the stupidity of the hypnotised cats!
Their cat distracting properties prove that televisions are still useful for something
Simply walk past a television to switch it on
It’s the same old re-run, day in, day out, but the cats don’t seem to notice
Imagine a future where a television is small enough to fit in the palm of your hand!
Agent Squeak once featured in his own television show ‘Dashing Mouse Likes Cheese’, it was cancelled for being too popular 
Pep yourself up with a chilli when your cheese trail weighs you down
Chow down on a chilli to get a boost of speed
This is, without a doubt, the hottest item in the game
Chilli peppers have been a part of the human diet since around 7500 B.C. but mice have been a part of the cat diet for far longer than that!\n
Two handy mobile hiding spots for our dashing mouse
If your mobile hiding spot starts to flash, you’d better find somewhere else to hide
Hide under these and you can stay on the move without being seen!
It was once said that you can’t hide in broad daylight… That’s probably true, so hide under one of these instead
It’s not quite clear why cats don’t seem surprised by moving teacups and buckets
‘Bucket drumming’ is where a person (or mouse) drums on large plastic buckets
It’s a big cannon that shoots mice
Good for quick getaways and reaching certain destinations by air (luck not included)
Use a cannon to reach an out-of-the-way area or make a quick escape
There aren’t many other forms of entertainment where you can watch a little mouse get fired out of a cannon
Agent Squeak does all his own stunts, even those involving cannons 
No cannons were harmed in the making of this game
Cats are pretty self-interested, everyone knows that, so give them a fish or some string and you’ll lose them for a while
Pick them up, add them to your trail, lead them to a cat and you can’t fail
Cats are easily distracted by the things they love, offer up a ball of string or a fish to a cat and buy some extra time
Fish can only be used once, but balls of string just keep on rolling
Fish are one time only cat-distraction, but balls of string can be used again and again
Fish! String! Cats love them! Mice just use them to get by…
Instructions: Find corresponding button, walk over it, recover cheese from machine. Easy!
Jump on the corresponding button and the Cheese Machine will cough up its cheese
The button is not always close to the machine, you might need to search for it
Cheese Machines: Keeping cheese fresh since 2011
Cheese Machines have yet to be invented as a real-life device, no-one knows why
Cheese Machines were once thought to be oversized fax machines that printed on cheese instead of paper
Run over buttons to open nearby doors and barricades
Some buttons have time limits, so plan carefully (and learn how to count)
Buttons and barricades are almost always colour coded
"Buttons, oh buttons, far and wide, without you, the world would be full of closed doors" (from Agent Squeak’s first - and last - poem ‘Buttons of my Travels’)
If ever in doubt, and there’s a button close by, step on it
You can use buttons to trap cats, but you can also trap yourself, so be careful
These buttons can only be operated by cats
Trick those silly cats into running over cat-shaped buttons. Hahahaha, stupid cats!
Lure an unsuspecting cat over one of these buttons to activate it
It’s a button… With a cat on it
Finally! A chance to step on a cat!
Cat buttons don't make very good pets
Looks a bit like our hero, but made of metal, not mouse
Use a fake mouse to spring a mousetrap and take the cheese
Wherever there is a mousetrap, there is a fake mouse close by
Our hero has been known to talk to fake mice (on his more lonely days)
Many, many aspiring mouse imitators auditioned for the fake mouse role in ‘SPY mouse’
Fake mice are the only known animals to strike fear into the hearts of fake elephants
Collect hidden dossiers for extra intel
Dossiers contain extra intel on cats and items, collect them all!
Find all the hidden dossiers to expand your SPY knowledge
"Update out now!"
"Global leaderboards!"
"Double the challenges!"
Collector
Brains & Brawn
Intelligence Expert
Field Expert
Find all the hidden dossiers!
Collect all the hidden dossiers!
Boss 1
Boss One
Mouse-mincer
Spin-o-bot
Cheese Grater
A villainous contraption built to make mince of a mouse!
An evil machine devised solely to smite our heroic mouse!
Lure this heinous machine to its slippery demise!
Use all your cunning to lure this baleful contraption to the oil slick!
It's quite a thing to destroy a machine with the very same oil that pulses through its cold, metal heart
If it loses sight of you, it loses interest, so make sure it can see you at all times!
If it turns its back on you, make a mouse of yourself and get its attention back!
Touch to view dossiers
Touch a dossier to view
Touch to view
Touch a card to view the dossier
Touch a card to view dossiers
Touch a card to view
SPY mouse HD
Enjoying SPY mouse HD?
Boss
Select language
English
Français
Italiano
Deutsch
Español
Nederlands
日本語
简体中文
한국어
More games
